http://www.alzforum.org/privacy-policy

The Alzforum website (the “Site”) collects information in order to serve you better--by providing better information and creating a valuable community in which to discuss ideas, issues and share data and expertise with other members. Any personal information we collect will be used solely to improve our services, and will not be sold to other companies without your consent. This privacy policy governs personal information collected by us on the Site as well as through any digital products and services or mobile applications that we may offer from time to time with respect to Alzforum.
What information we gather and how we gather it
How we use and disclose your information
Opt-in/Opt-out
Reviewing or changing your information/Profile Page
Improper Conduct
Protection for Children
Your Consent
Contacting Us
1. What Information We Gather and How We Gather It
Membership Application and Online Registration. To process your Alzforum membership and/or your online registration, we may ask you to provide common required information including name, email address, etc.
Automatically Collected Information. We collect data about the movement of users on the Site. This may include the Internet Protocol Address of your computer, host name, domain name, browser version and platform, date and time of requests and files downloaded or viewed. We use this information to analyze usage of the Site. We also use cookies to collect information and personalize your experience on the Site. We store a limited amount of personal information in cookies.
2. How We Use and Disclose Your Information
We do not sell your personally identifiable information to third parties or mass marketers. For example, we will not sell another company your name or email address. On occasions, we may ask for your consent to share particular data with a third party. In addition, we reserve the right, without disclosing your personally identifiable information to third parties, to use the information you provide to offer you additional Alzforum or third party products and services that we think will be of interest to you.
We do disclose aggregated data to our sponsors and co-branded partners to generate reports and marketing research. For example, we tell funding agencies how many people visit the Site or specific parts of the Site. Where available, we may offer additional information about viewer characteristics. However this does not include personally identifiable information about you or your online usage patterns.
If you choose to receive the free Alzforum Newsletter as set forth below (see “Opt-in/Opt-out”), we will use these newsletters to provide you with news, events, special offers, site upgrades and much more.
On occasion, we may use the content you post in the Site’s community section including chat rooms and discussions or any other public section of the Site for promotional purposes, in email newsletters, in promotional collateral, or elsewhere and by using the Site you agree that we may do so. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in these areas.
We may share your personally identifiable information with third parties with which we contract to help enhance the functionality of the Site and provide new products, services and content. For example, we use third parties for webinar registration and for newsletter generation. We make sure that these third parties do not use this information for any other purpose and do not share the information with any other third party. These third parties must maintain the confidentiality of your personal information and have access to your personal information only to the extent necessary to perform the function that we have requested.
3. Security Measures
We take measures to secure the personal information that users submit on the Site. We encrypt such information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
4. Opt-in/Opt-out
You have the option to sign up for the free Alzforum Newsletter by submitting your email address via the Newsletter sign-up page on the Site or by checking the box on your Site profile page.
To opt out from receiving these emails, you can click on the link located at the bottom of the email newsletter or change your profile on the Site.
We are not responsible for removing information from third-party lists or databases.
5. Reviewing or Changing Your Information
In order to ensure that the information we maintain is accurate, the Site gives users the option to change or modify their previously provided information. Users can manage their profile in the MyXForum area of the Site. Site editors have access to the users’ profile changes. Users can submit corrections to comments that they previously posted on the Site.
6. Improper Conduct
The restrictions above will not apply in the event that you engage in certain improper conduct. Specifically, we shall have the right ourselves to use or release to third parties personally identifiable information regarding users who are suspected of having used the Site for any fraudulent purposes or having otherwise violated any law rule or regulation.
7. Protection for Children
We have no intention of collecting personally identifiable information from children (i.e., individuals under the age of 13).  If a child has provided us with individually identifiable information, that child's parent or guardian should Contact Us to have this information deleted from our records.
8. Your Consent
By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Alzforum in the manner explained above. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on the Site so you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Use of the Site constitutes consent to the Privacy Policy then in effect.
9. Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Site, or your dealings with the Site, please Contact Us.
Scientific Advisory Board2011-2016 Scientific Advisory Board
